<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<activity id="635" moduleid="146955" modulename="lesson" contextid="220437">
  <lesson id="635">
    <course>3115</course>
    <name>Lesson #0</name>
    <intro>&lt;p&gt;You need to do the Getting to Know You Survey before doing this.  This Lesson will help you get oriented in the course.  It is not worth any marks, but most of the moodle activities in the course will be locked until you complete this lesson and Quiz #0, which this links to.  It will:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;guide you to some important parts of the course outline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;point you at some features of moodle which will be useful to know&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;help you set up some software which you will need in the course&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;make sure that you have been informed about academic integrity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can redo this lesson any time you want if you want to review some of the information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before you start the lesson I strongly suggest that you open the course outline in another browser tab so that you can refer to it during the lesson without closing the lesson.  To do this (on a computer - it is possible on a phone but more awkward), right click on one of the links to the course outline and then from the drop down menu choose "Open link in new tab".&lt;/p&gt;</intro>
    <introformat>1</introformat>
    <practice>0</practice>
    <modattempts>0</modattempts>
    <usepassword>0</usepassword>
    <password></password>
    <dependency>0</dependency>
    <conditions>O:8:"stdClass":3:{s:9:"timespent";i:0;s:9:"completed";i:0;s:15:"gradebetterthan";i:0;}</conditions>
    <grade>100</grade>
    <custom>1</custom>
    <ongoing>0</ongoing>
    <usemaxgrade>1</usemaxgrade>
    <maxanswers>6</maxanswers>
    <maxattempts>3</maxattempts>
    <review>0</review>
    <nextpagedefault>0</nextpagedefault>
    <feedback>0</feedback>
    <minquestions>6</minquestions>
    <maxpages>1</maxpages>
    <timelimit>0</timelimit>
    <retake>1</retake>
    <activitylink>146956</activitylink>
    <mediafile></mediafile>
    <mediaheight>480</mediaheight>
    <mediawidth>640</mediawidth>
    <mediaclose>0</mediaclose>
    <slideshow>0</slideshow>
    <width>640</width>
    <height>480</height>
    <bgcolor>#FFFFFF</bgcolor>
    <displayleft>0</displayleft>
    <displayleftif>0</displayleftif>
    <progressbar>0</progressbar>
    <available>0</available>
    <deadline>0</deadline>
    <timemodified>1631750000</timemodified>
    <completionendreached>1</completionendreached>
    <completiontimespent>0</completiontimespent>
    <allowofflineattempts>0</allowofflineattempts>
    <pages>
      <page id="9278">
        <prevpageid>0</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9279</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594141095</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1630511771</timemodified>
        <title>Main Menu</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;Please select one of the buttons below to choose a part of this lesson.  You can do them in any order and you can revisit parts that you have already done.  Some parts will ask you questions.  Note that there is no mark for this lesson.  So if you get the questions wrong it is just feedback to let you know that there is something you have not understood.  I suggest that you do the part about the Course Outline last as it will ask you to click a button which will take you to Quiz #0 about the course outline, which is separate from this lesson.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21136">
            <jumpto>9279</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594141095</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Academic Integrity</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21137">
            <jumpto>9286</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594141095</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Getting to know some features of moodle</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21138">
            <jumpto>9287</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594141095</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Software you will need for this course</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21139">
            <jumpto>9296</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594141095</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>The Course Outline (do this part last)</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9279">
        <prevpageid>9278</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9280</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594226743</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1631109611</timemodified>
        <title>Academic Integrity</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;Academic integrity is central to everything we do at a university.  I believe that it is crucial that you understand, and have reflected upon the principles of academic integrity.  You are required to complete the Introduction to Academic Integrity moodle course.  If you have already completed it this year then you should already have the Academic Integrity Badge (2021/2022).  If  you have not completed it, or if you did it in a previous year, then you will not have the badge.  You will not be given access to a lot of things on this course  moodle if you don't have this badge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you think you have the badge (i.e. if you completed the Intro. to Academic Integrity course very recently) then you can verify this.  If you are on a computer (this is harder on a phone...) click your name in the upper right corner of the window.  Right click "Profile" and choose "Open link in new tab", so that you will go to your profile without leaving this page.  In your profile, just under your e-mail address there will be a Badges area, if you have earned any badges.  It should look like this (except it shows the Academic Citizenship Badge, which is what the integrity badge was called last year):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/profile_with_badge.png" width="500" height="323" alt="badge" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the badges area is not there, or if the Academic Integrity Badge (2021/2022) is not there, then you need to complete the Intro. to  Academic Integrity course.  If the badge is  there, then you are good to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need to complete the Introduction to Academic Integrity course then it will likely only take you about 20 minutes.  Here is a link to it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="$@COURSEVIEWBYID*849@$"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="$@COURSEVIEWBYID*4089@$" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-auth="NotApplicable" title="$@COURSEVIEWBYID*4089@$" data-linkindex="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;$@COURSEVIEWBYID*4089@$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To enter it you will need an enrolment key.  The enrolment key is: capers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It might take a couple of minutes after you complete the course for the badge to show up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The focus of the Intro. to Academic Integrity course will have been on correct citation practices when writing papers.  That will be a major concern for you in many courses, however it isn't a major concern in this course because you will not be writing papers.  The things that are concerns in this course are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Copying assignment solutions (from other students, from online sources, or from solutions manuals)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cheating on exams (using materials which are not allowed during the exam, or communicating with others during the exam)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Various forms of dishonesty which can occur in lab reports, such as fabrication of data, or copying analysis or answers to questions from other students.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The underlying principle here is the same as the underlying principle for correct citation when you are writing papers - we must never claim other people's work as our own.  This is why we cite the work of others when we use their words or ideas in papers that we write.  It is also why everything you submit in assignments, exams, and labs must be your own work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are grey areas here which can be difficult to navigate.  Let me be clear that, while I am going to keep a very close eye out for violations of academic integrity, I am not "out to get you".  In particular, I recognize the grey areas.  If I think you are straying into a grey area, I will give you a warning.  No hard feelings!  However, if I see clear signs of academic misconduct then I  will follow CBU's policies for dealing with academic misconduct.  If you have completed the Introduction to Academic Integrity course then you should now be aware of what the penalties are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because there are grey areas, and some expectations can vary a bit from course to course, I have written a bit about this in the course outline to try to clarify my expectations.  Please read the relevant part of the course outline (in another browser tab) before going on to some questions which will help ensure that you have read and understood.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21141">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594226743</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go on to questions</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9280">
        <prevpageid>9279</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9282</nextpageid>
        <qtype>3</qtype>
        <qoption>1</qoption>
        <layout>0</layout>
        <display>0</display>
        <timecreated>1594738802</timecreated>
        <timemodified>0</timemodified>
        <title>Which are examples of academic misconduct?</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;This will be quite similar to a question you answered in the Introduction to Academic Integrity course, but is more focused on things which are directly relevant to this course.  Which of the following are examples of academic misconduct (select all that apply)?&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21145">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594738802</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Copying another student's work&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;Yes.  This is one of the most common forms of academic misconduct that I have seen in this course in the past.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21146">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594738802</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Allowing another student to copy your work&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;Yes. Help your fellow students. But don't damage their learning by doing their work for them.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21147">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594738802</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Copying and pasting from an online source into any document that you are submitting for marks&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;Yes.  This is not so common in this course since most work you submit will be hand-written.  But I have seen it at times.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21148">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594738802</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Copying assignment solutions from solutions manuals or online sources such as "homework help" sites&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;Yes.  In recent years this has become the most common form of academic misconduct that I catch.  The most common source for students copying assignment solutions is Chegg.  Note that I have an explicit policy stated in the course outline for Chegg and other similar "homework help" sites.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21149">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594738802</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Helping another student on an assignment&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;No. Helping each other is encouraged.  But note that just giving someone the answer is not helping.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21150">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594738802</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Receiving help from another student on an assignment&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;No. Helping each other is encouraged.  But note that if they just give you the answer that is not helping.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21151">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594738802</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Asking the professor for help during an exam&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;No. I'm happy to give clarifications of questions during the exams.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9282">
        <prevpageid>9280</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9285</nextpageid>
        <qtype>3</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>0</layout>
        <display>0</display>
        <timecreated>1594739841</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1631897980</timemodified>
        <title>The Chegg  rule</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;Scenario: You are working on Assignment #3 in this course.  One of your classmates texts you saying, "Someone has posted problem 2 on Chegg." &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You reply, "Is the answer posted?"  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Not yet," they reply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What should you do, and why?&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21152">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>1</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594739841</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Keep working on the problem.  It may still be worth it to hand it in.&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;Yes.  Depending on several factors I may decide that the problem will still count for marks, but if the solutions is posted I will carefully police submitted solutions to see whether anyone copied from Chegg.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21153">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594739841</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Stop working on the problem since it won't count for marks.&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;No.  It may still count for marks.  I will take several factors into consideration when I am deciding whether the question will count for marks or not.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21154">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594739841</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Stop working on the question, find the question on Chegg and bookmark it so you can check back later to see if the solution is posted.  If a solution is posted, copy it down.&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;That's plagiarism.  Don't do it.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21155">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>1</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594739841</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Tell Geoff that the question has been posted.&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;Sure.  I'll almost certainly find it myself, but I do appreciate it if you point it out to me and save me a bit of time.  But also, keep working on the question since it may still count for marks.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9285">
        <prevpageid>9282</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9286</nextpageid>
        <qtype>10</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>0</layout>
        <display>0</display>
        <timecreated>1594738261</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1594778270</timemodified>
        <title>Pledge of Academic Integrity</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please make a pledge that you will act with integrity in all matters pertaining to the course.  This is not optional.  I will check these pledges and if anyone has skipped it I will ask them to revisit this page and write a pledge.  &lt;/span&gt;It is up to you to come up with what you think is reasonable wording. It doesn't need to be long, but I'm looking for you to make it clear that you understand the issues and take them seriously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you have finished typing, the Submit button below will take you back to the Main Menu.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21144">
            <jumpto>9278</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>1</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594738261</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>$@NULL@$</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9289">
        <prevpageid>9283</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9290</nextpageid>
        <qtype>5</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>0</layout>
        <display>0</display>
        <timecreated>1594771631</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1631062718</timemodified>
        <title>Match items to dates</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;It will be very useful to keep an eye on the calendar in moodle.  I have placed all of the important dates for the course, including due dates, on the calendar and I will do my best to keep the calendar up-to-date if anything changes.  In the other browser tab, which is currently pointed at the main moodle page, notice that there is an area called "Upcoming events" (likely on the left side of your screen if you haven't reconfigured anything).  At the bottom of that area click the link that says "Go to calendar...".  You should now be looking at a more detailed list of upcoming  events.  However, more usefully (I think) on the right side of the screen you will see monthly views.  Dates with events on them will be highlighted and if you hover over them they will show you what events are on those dates.  You can see an expanded view of this.  Click on the link to September to go to a detailed monthly view of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use  the calendar to match the events listed below to their correct dates.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21156">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>1</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594771631</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Yup.  You can read a calendar.&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21157">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594771631</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Did you find your way to the calendar?&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21158">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594771631</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Start Unit #3 - Vectors&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>Wed., Sept. 22</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21159">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594771631</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Assignment #1 due&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>Thurs., Sept. 16</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21160">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594771631</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;Midterm #1 during class&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>Wed., Oct. 6</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9283">
        <prevpageid>9284</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9289</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594773062</timecreated>
        <timemodified>0</timemodified>
        <title>Time zone</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;On the page where you have been editing your profile there is a box for setting your time zone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully what that box says is "Server timezone (America/Glace Bay)".  If that's what it says then everything is good.  Hit the "Update profile" button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it doesn't say that then you probably want to change it.  But give it a moment's thought first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are in Cape Breton (or nearby, such as Halifax) then you &lt;strong&gt;definitely&lt;/strong&gt; want to be in the server timezone.  So change it so it is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are not in Cape Breton, and especially if you are far from Cape Breton (e.g. India) then maybe you want to change it and maybe you don't.  Moodle will translate all due dates into your time zone.  This is probably convenient.  But it will mean that the due dates listed on the moodle calendar may not match all of the due dates on documents, such as assignments, and Mastery Task due dates listed in the course outline.  Decide whether which option you will find less confusing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you've adjusted your timezone, hit the "Update profile" button.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21166">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594773062</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go to next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9286">
        <prevpageid>9285</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9284</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594483700</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1599483019</timemodified>
        <title>Getting to Know Some Features in Moodle</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;This section of the lesson is going to get you a bit more oriented in moodle.  It will be getting you to visit various other pages in moodle, but for simplicity you probably shouldn't  leave this lesson as you are doing this.  So you will need to open other tabs in your browser.  You &lt;strong&gt;can&lt;/strong&gt; do that on a phone but it is a bit awkward.  So I suggest doing this part of the lesson on a computer, not on a phone.  Hopefully, if you didn't know how to open other browser tabs before starting this assignment, you should now since you should have opened the course outline in another tab.  You should open the main PHYS 1101 page in another tab right now.  The easiest way to do this will be to use the navigation links just under the course title at the top of the page.  At the top of the page you should see  a sequence of links looking roughly like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Home / My courses / 2020 Fall / PHYS-1101-0.2020F / Preparatory Material...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use the PHYS-1101-0.2020F link to open the main course page in another tab.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21143">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594483700</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go on to the next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9284">
        <prevpageid>9286</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9283</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594772647</timecreated>
        <timemodified>0</timemodified>
        <title>Add your picture</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;It can be a bit harder to get to know each other in an online course than it would be in a face-to-face course.  But there are things we can do to fix that.  As you will hopefully see, there will actually be quite a bit of one-on-one interaction in this course, both with me and with your classmates.  As a first step to helping people get to know each other, it is useful for everyone to have an avatar.  The best choice is probably to use a picture of your face as your avatar, so that we all start to connect names to faces.  But if you are not comfortable doing that use some other avatar, such  as a drawing.  To do this, using the other tab, click on your name in the upper right corner of the window.  From the drop down list choose "profile".  In the User details area, click the link that says "edit profile".  This will bring you to a page where you can upload a user picture.  While you are at it, if the name listed  on moodle isn't the name you would prefer to use you might as well change that as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't hit the "Update profile" button yet.  There is still one more thing to check.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21165">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594772647</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go to the next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9288">
        <prevpageid>9287</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9291</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594774884</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1599492295</timemodified>
        <title>Log in to e-mail</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;On the CBU website, in the upper right corner is a "Login" link.  Click that and select "Office 365 e-mail".  Your login id and password for your e-mail should be the same as for moodle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you are in your Outlook e-mail, you actually have access to a lot more than just e-mail, because you are in Office 365 which is a suite of programs which run via your browser.  I'm actually not a big fan of Microsoft, but I have to grudgingly admit that Office 365 is pretty good.  In the upper left corner of Office 365 you will see a button that looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/app_launcher.png" width="45" height="43" alt="app launcher button" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's the app launcher button.  Click it and you will see a drop down list which gives you access to other applications.  The ones you will probably use the most in this course are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OneDrive (your cloud drive where you can store your files and have easy access to them everywhere)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teams (more about this later, but it is where we will hold classes using video conferencing and we will also use it for a lot of other communication)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excel (spreadsheet)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start by opening OneDrive.  Let's start getting you organized.  Create a folder in OneDrive called "phys1101".  Then click into that folder.  In that folder create another folder called "labs".  Throughout the term, as you are working on labs in this course I suggest that you put all the files in this folder so that they are easy to find.  Create any other folders inside your phys1101 folder that you think might be useful.  If they don't  turn out to be useful you can always delete them later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a short video produced by CBU's Centre for Teaching and Learning which you might find helpful for learning the basics of Office 365.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gjrLKoEDKlg&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21168">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594774884</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go to next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9291">
        <prevpageid>9288</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9292</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1596120801</timecreated>
        <timemodified>0</timemodified>
        <title>Set an autoforward</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;Although there are increasingly other ways that people are communicating in professional environments, e-mail remains one of the main ways.  I will try to restrict most of the course-related communication in this course to Teams and moodle.  However, I may need to contact you via e-mail.  Also, your campus e-mail is the official channel for CBU to contact you.  So it is important that you check your campus e-mail regularly.  This is a hard habit to develop.  If you have another e-mail address that you do regularly check then a solution is to have all of your CBU e-mail autoforwarded to that address.  So the next thing you should do is set an autoforward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In your campus e-mail (Outlook) click the gear icon in the upper right which looks like this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/outlook_settings.png" width="53" height="66" alt="Outlook settings button" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the drop down menu that this opens, click into the search field.  Type "forward" and then select "Forwarding" which will be presented as an option.  A dialogue window will open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select "Enable forwarding" then enter your preferred e-mail address into the text box. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click the Save button.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21175">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1596120801</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go to the next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9290">
        <prevpageid>9289</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9287</nextpageid>
        <qtype>3</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>0</layout>
        <display>0</display>
        <timecreated>1594772079</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1594773095</timemodified>
        <title>The grades</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;Find your way to where you can view your grades.  Where did you find it?&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21162">
            <jumpto>9278</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>1</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594772079</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;The "Grades" link in the Navigation area (just under the Upcoming events area)&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;Yup.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21163">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594772079</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;In the Preparatory Material and General Course Information section&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;No.  It's not there.  Keep looking.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21164">
            <jumpto>0</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594772079</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>&lt;p&gt;In your Dashboard (accessed from the Navigation area)&lt;/p&gt;</answer_text>
            <response>&lt;p&gt;No.  It's not there.  Keep looking.&lt;/p&gt;</response>
            <answerformat>1</answerformat>
            <responseformat>1</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9287">
        <prevpageid>9290</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9288</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594773366</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1594773412</timemodified>
        <title>Software setup</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;Because the course is being run online, we will rely a bit more than usual on you having various pieces of software on your own computer.  In a normal year some these would be things that you would use on computers in the lab.  This part of the lesson will direct you to install some software which you will need, or likely find useful.  It will also start to get you oriented with Office 365, which every CBU student automatically has access to.  Open the main CBU web page in another tab.  Here's a link to help you do that quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cbu.ca"&gt;LINK TO CBU WEB PAGE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21167">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594773366</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go to the next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9292">
        <prevpageid>9291</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>10217</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594776486</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1631056645</timemodified>
        <title>Open Teams</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;Last year, when the course was offered entirely remotely, students needed Teams.  This year I still expect that you will find  it useful for communicating with me outside of class time.  It is much more efficient than e-mail.  So, even though we  won't use  it during class time I would still like you all to install Teams on your computers and/or phones.  I  will push you all to communicate with me via Teams rather than  e-mail.  The instructions below are for installing Teams on a computer.  Installing it on your phone is easier so I will leave that up to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Office 365, open Teams.  You might want to watch this video which was produced by the CBU Centre for Teaching and Learning (15 min):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qkJWsvjIyXI&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Office 365 will probably offer you the opportunity to install the desktop app, so you can run it locally on your computer instead of running it through a browser.  The desktop app is more capable than the web app.  I &lt;strong&gt;highly&lt;/strong&gt; recommend that you install it.  If you've already got the desktop app then just open that.  If Office 365 offers you the opportunity to install it then follow the instructions to do so.  If it doesn't then you can download it and install it from here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-ca/microsoft-365/microsoft-teams/download-app"&gt;ALTERNATE LINK TO DOWNLOAD TEAMS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you are in Teams, if you haven't already joined the Team for this course then you should do so.  From the main page in Teams, which lists all of the Teams you are in, there is a button in the upper right corner that looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/join_team.png" width="208" height="50" alt="join team" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click that.  It will present you with a few options.  One of them is to "Join a team with a code", which will look like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/enter_code.png" width="281" height="270" alt="enter code" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To join the PHYS 1101 team, enter this code in that box: ja10y8m&lt;span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: x-small;"&gt;In the PHYS 1101 team, under the Posts tab, say hello to everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: x-small;"&gt;On the right side of the page in Teams, there will be a Calendar tab.  Click that and look around.  You should already see our classes on the calendar, every Monday.  Sorry, I couldn't figure out how to not schedule them on Thanksgiving and during Reading Week, so just ignore those ones.  Clicking into those on the calendar in Teams is one of the easiest ways to join the class meetings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: x-small;"&gt;You may also want to install Teams on your phone.  You can do that through Google Play or the Apple Store.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21169">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594776486</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="10217">
        <prevpageid>9292</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9297</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1630511661</timecreated>
        <timemodified>0</timemodified>
        <title>Send me a chat message in Teams</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;Please send me a personal chat message in Teams to establish contact.  In Teams (on a computer - it works differently on a phone) on the left side of the screen are a number of tabs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Activity&lt;br /&gt;Chat&lt;br /&gt;Teams&lt;br /&gt;Assignments&lt;br /&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click the Chat tab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now at the top of the left column will be an icon to start a new chat that looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/Screenshot%20from%202021-09-01%2011-41-18.png" width="500" height="255" alt="top left corner of Teams, showing start new chat button" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click that.  In the text box that opens start typing my name, "Geoffrey Lee-...".  As you type you will be  presented with options in a drop down list.  So once you see my name in the list, select it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, towards the bottom of the page, click into the textbox and type a message to me.  I will reply when I see your message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be your default way of contacting me outside of regular hours.  Please use this, not phone or e-mail.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="23382">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1630511661</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="10215">
        <prevpageid>9293</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9296</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1630365282</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1631478681</timemodified>
        <title>Online shared whiteboard</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;We may make use of an online, shared whiteboard.  To create a whiteboard you need  to have an account on the whiteboard website.  For example, if you want to complete Mastery Tasks at times when I am not on campus then this will be necessary.   The accounts are free.  Go to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://miro.com"&gt;miro.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and create an account.  If it tells you that you need to upgrade (and pay...) then ignore it.  The free account will do everything you need.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="23380">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1630365282</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go to next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9281">
        <prevpageid>9295</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>0</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594951372</timecreated>
        <timemodified>0</timemodified>
        <title>Done?</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;If you think you are finished the lesson (have you done all four parts?) then clicking the "I am finished" button will take you onward to a short quiz about the course outline.  It is the last thing you will need to complete to gain access to the rest of the course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't think you are finished with the lesson then click the other button which will take you back to the Main Menu.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21172">
            <jumpto>-9</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594951372</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>I am finished - take me to the Course Outline quiz</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
          <answer id="21173">
            <jumpto>9278</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594951372</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go back to the Main Menu</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9295">
        <prevpageid>9296</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9281</nextpageid>
        <qtype>10</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>0</layout>
        <display>0</display>
        <timecreated>1594396570</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1631056760</timemodified>
        <title>Write a question</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;Look at the list of unanswered questions at the beginning of the course outline. Now in the space below write your own question.  Don't  repeat one of the questions from the course outline - write your own.  It doesn't have to be an unanswered question (you probably don't know whether it is answered or not). But it should be a question, related to physics, that you want to know the answer to.  To be clear, I don't mean a question about the course, or the structure of the course.  I mean a question about the principles and/or applications of physics.  So for example something like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"What are the most important things we will learn in this course?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"What happens if we miss an assignment deadline?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;are &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; questions about physics, they are questions about the course.  Please write a question about physics.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21142">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>1</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594396570</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>$@NULL@$</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9293">
        <prevpageid>9297</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>10215</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594955837</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1631056699</timemodified>
        <title>Scanning app</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;For this course, and perhaps for others, you will need to be able to submit multi-page, hand-written documents (word processors are notoriously bad at typing equations, and their ability to make diagrams might be worse).  To do this you will need to use your phone to take pictures of the documents.  However, if you just do this normally you will end up with multiple image files which you would need to upload.  Uploading multiple files like this will be annoying for you.  It will also be annoying for me - it would essentially be like handing in paper assignments without stapling them.  Also, many of the applications you will need to submit these documents to will only allow you to upload a single file.  So, instead of submitting multiple image files you need to package all of the pictures into a single file.  The easy way to do this is to use a scanner app for your phone which will convert your multiple pictures into a single pdf file.  There are a lot of scanner apps that you can install for free from Google Play or the Apple Store.  I've tried a few of them and here are my thoughts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adobe Scan&lt;/strong&gt;: this is the one I think is best.  It is free and won't try to sell you a pay version.  It is easy to use and has all the features you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Lens&lt;/strong&gt;: this one is good.  Not sure whether it is available for i-phone.  I don't think it is quite as easy to use as Adobe Scan, but you may have a different experience.  Try it if you don't like Adobe Scan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CamScanner&lt;/strong&gt;: I have seen a lot of students use this.  I tried it and I &lt;strong&gt;hate it&lt;/strong&gt;!  It is very difficult to use (in my opinion) and it is constantly trying to get you to upgrade to a pay version.  You'll see lots of people and websites recommend it.  I suspect they are being paid to do so.  Don't get fished in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Install a scanner app on your phone.  My recommendation is Adobe Scan, but if there is something you like better then use it.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21174">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594955837</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go to next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9296">
        <prevpageid>10215</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9295</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594226360</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1631056735</timemodified>
        <title>Course outline</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;This part of the assignment will hopefully familiarize you with some things in the Course Outline.  It is fairly typical that when students receive course outlines, they look at how the mark in the course is going to be calculated, then stuff the course outline in their backpack and never look at it again.  Because I'm running a bit of an oddball course, this isn't a good idea in this course.  You should open the course outline in another browser tab and look it over before you proceed.  If you are not sure how to do this, here's a quick explanation.  If you are on a phone these instructions won't work.  I recommend doing this on a computer;  it is possible on a phone, but awkward.  At the top of the page is a navigation area that should look like&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Home/My courses/ 2020 Fall / PHYS-1101-0.2020F / Preparatory Material and General Course Information / Assignment #0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On that thing at the top of the page right click "Preparatory Material and General Course Information" and choose "open link in new tab".  In the new tab, open the course outline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a moment to look through the Course Outline.  I'd like you to notice the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What are the policies for missed/late assignments, activities, labs, etc.?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How can I be contacted?  Would I like you to contact me frequently?  If you have questions about the course and/or assignments, where are the best places to ask those questions?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why do I use video lectures?  Should you expect me to spend time in class introducing the basic ideas of the course?  Why or why not?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What are the goals of the course?  Am I making it hard to figure out what my expectations are in each topic unit?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should you work on assignments by yourself?  What are my expectations with regards to academic integrity?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you've had a look over the course outline, go on to the next page.  You will be asked some questions to make sure that you have understood the course outline.  Note that there is no mark for these questions, but you won't be allowed to leave any question until you have answered it correctly.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21140">
            <jumpto>9295</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594226360</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Go on to the questions</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
      <page id="9297">
        <prevpageid>10217</prevpageid>
        <nextpageid>9293</nextpageid>
        <qtype>20</qtype>
        <qoption>0</qoption>
        <layout>1</layout>
        <display>1</display>
        <timecreated>1594777303</timecreated>
        <timemodified>1630364911</timemodified>
        <title>LibreOffice</title>
        <contents>&lt;p&gt;You will use a spreadsheet quite a bit during the labs.  You already have access to one through Office 365.  However, in the lab you will need to use a different spreadsheet since:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you might want to use a spreadsheet when you don't have an internet connection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the web version of Excel that you have in Office 365 isn't quite as full featured as a desktop app.  In particular it can't do trend lines on graphs, which you will need to do in many labs. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will mostly use this in the lab, and you can use it on the computers in the lab.  However, it may be convenient for you to have it installed on your own computer since  you might like to bring  your laptop to the lab, and there will be assignment questions where you will find it useful to have a spreadsheet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've already got Excel, or something similar installed on your computer then good.  If you don't a free option is to install LibreOffice.  This is a free, open source office suite which includes a spreadsheet.  The spreadsheet in LibreOffice is fairly equivalent to Excel, though the interface is a bit different.  You can download LibreOffice (for Windows, Mac, or Linux) from here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.libreoffice.org/download/download/"&gt;DOWNLOAD LIBREOFFICE&lt;/a&gt; (right click and open in new tab to avoid leaving this page)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The spreadsheet in LibreOffice is called LibreOffice Calc.  If you are already familiar with spreadsheets then, great!  If not, don't worry.  We will give you an introduction to spreadsheet use during the first lab.&lt;/p&gt;</contents>
        <contentsformat>1</contentsformat>
        <answers>
          <answer id="21170">
            <jumpto>-1</jumpto>
            <grade>0</grade>
            <score>0</score>
            <flags>0</flags>
            <timecreated>1594777303</timecreated>
            <timemodified>0</timemodified>
            <answer_text>Next page</answer_text>
            <response>$@NULL@$</response>
            <answerformat>0</answerformat>
            <responseformat>0</responseformat>
            <attempts>
            </attempts>
          </answer>
        </answers>
        <branches>
        </branches>
      </page>
    </pages>
    <grades>
    </grades>
    <timers>
    </timers>
    <overrides>
    </overrides>
  </lesson>
</activity>